A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Diane Van Wie, Series 34 FA373
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Meetings, Luncheons, and Dinners, 1958-1973; 06; 21 document box(es)
  - Colorado Trip, May 12-13, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1492)
  - Capital District Tour, May 23, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1493)
  - Capital District Tour, May 24, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1494)
  - Luncheon for Japanese Governors, May 24, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1495)
  - Dinner for Communications People, May 24, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1496)
  - Breakfast for Labor Leaders, May 25, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1497)
  - New York Young Republicans Banquet, May 25, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1498)
  - Capital District Tour, May 25, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1499)
  - Westchester Community College - Valhalla, June 10, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1500)
  - Luncheon Conference on School Fallout Shelters Program, June 11, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1501)
  - Annual Health Conference, June 12, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1502)
  - New York Republican State Committee Dinner, June 14, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1503)
  - Cabinet Meetings and Luncheon, June 25, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1504)
  - Governors' Conference, July 1-4, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1505)
  - Banquet of Council of Bishops African Methodist Episcopal Church, July 5, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1506)
  - Candidates Conference, Washington, DC, July 6, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1507)
  - Meeting with Fashion Leaders about World's Fair, July 9, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1508)
  - Luncheon Given by Thomas Dewey, July 9, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1509)
  - Conference of Federation of Women's Republican Clubs, August 3, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1510)
  - New York State Sheriffs' Association Annual Conference, August 7, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1511)
  - Visit Orange County Fair, August 8, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1512)
  - Visit Chenango County Fair, August 8, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1513)
  - Oswego County Republican Committee Chicken Barbeque, August 9, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1514)
  - Fulton Chamber of Commerce Luncheon, August 9, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1515)
  - New York Republican State Convention, September 19, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1516)
  - White House Conference on Narcotics and Drug Abuse, September 27, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1517)
  - Campaign Rally, Amsterdam, September 28, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1518)
  - Groundbreaking, World's Fair, New York State Pavalion, October 9, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1519)
  - Luncheon Sponsored by National Republican Club, October 9, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1520)
  - Dinner for William E. Miller, October 23, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 1521)
  - Election Day Buffet, Hotel Roosevelt, November 6, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 1522)
  - Labor Leaders Dinner, November 27, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 1523)
  - Cabinet Luncheon, December 7, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 1524)
  - Arts and Entertainment Committee Dinner, December 11, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 1525)
  - Urban League Dinner of Greater New York, December 13, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 1526)
  - Buffet for Legislators - Mansion, January 9, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1527)
  - New York State Women's Joint Legislative Forum, January 15, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1528)
  - New York State Agricultural Society Dinner, January 16, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1529)
  - Dinner for Labor Leaders, Mansion, January 21, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1530)
  - Breakfast for Republican Legislators, Mansion, January 22, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1531)
  - Legislative Correspondents Dinner, Mansion, January 22, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1532)
  - Budget Luncheon, Mansion, January 28, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1533)
  - Breakfast for Republican Legislators, Mansion, January 29, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1534)
  - Reception for Architects, Mansion, January 29, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1535)
  - New York State Publishers Association Dinner, January 29, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1536)
  - Republican Victory Dinner, January 30, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1537)
  - American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Legislative Conference, February 4, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1538)
  - Breakfast for Republican Legislators, February 5, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1539)
  - Prayer Breakfast, February 5, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1540)
  - Marion Anderson Reception, February 10, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1541)
  - New York State Council of Churches, February 11, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1542)
  - Republican Chairmen and Vice Chairmen Luncheon, February 18, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1543)
  - Republican Chairmen and Vice Chairmen Luncheon, February 19, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1544)
  - Annual New York American Legion Legislative Dinner, February 19, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1545)
  - Legislative Reception, February 26, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 1546)
  - Prince Albert Reception, February 28, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1547)
  - Inner Circle Show, March 2, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1548)
  - Advisory Council for the Advancement of Industrial Research and Development, Farmingdale, March 7, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1549)
  - Moreland Commissioner Luncheon, March 11, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1550)
  - Associated Industries Luncheon, March 12, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1551)
  - County Officers Association Annual Conference, March 25, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1552)
  - Dinner for Judges of the Court of Appeals, March 26, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1553)
  - Briefing Conference on Agriculture, March 26, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1554)
  - South Mall Presentation, April 23, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1555)
  - Luncheon with Herald Tribune Editorial Staff, April 24, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1556)
  - Cincinnati Statement, April 29, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1557)
  - Counsel's Staff Dinner, April 30, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1558)
  - Community Blood Council of Greater New York, May 2, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1559)
  - Breakfast Meeting at Music Hall, May 3, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1560)
  - Cocktail Party for Members of the Press, June 3, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1561)
  - Dinner for the Citizens Planning Committee for Greater Albany, June 3, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1562)
  - Governor's Luncheon for Republican State Committee, June 6, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1563)
  - Personnel Council Award, June 11, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1564)
  - Dinner at Pocantico Hills, June 17, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1565)
  - Dedication of Port of Oswego and of Alroll, June 21, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1566)
  - Joseph Carlino Scholarship Fund Dinner, June 27, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1567)
  - Urban Transportation Planning Conference - Capitol, June 1, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1568)
  - Downtown Albany Luncheon, July 15, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1569)
  - Governors' Conference - Miami Beach, July 20-24, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1570)
  - Bohemian Encampment - California, July 27, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1571)
  - Private Meeting, September 12, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1572)
  - Denver, Colorado, September 13, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1573)
  - European Trip, September-October, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1574)
  - New York State Industrial Growth Conference - Council of Retail Merchants, October 8, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1575)
  - Dinner at Pocantico Hills, October 15, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1576)
  - Dinner - Pilgrims of the United States, November 6, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 1577)
  - Meeting of the Commerce and Industry Association of New York Inc., New York, New York, November 21, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 1578)
  - Westchester County Association Annual Membership Meeting, November 26, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 1579)
  - Dinner for Technical People - Music Hall, December 19, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 1580)
  - Buffet for Legislators Executive Mansion, Albany, New York, January 8, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1581)
  - Message to the Legislature, January 8, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1582)
  - Legislative Luncheon Meeting, New York State Association for Mental Health, Hotel Ten Eyck, Albany, New York, January 14, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1583)
  - New York State Women's Council Tea, Executive Mansion, January 14, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1584)
  - "On the Record" Interview, the "Detroit News", "Newark News", "St. Louis Post Dispatch", " Washington Star", January 17, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1585)
  - Budget Luncheon Executive Mansion, Albany, New York, January 20, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1586)
  - World Trade Center Model Unveiling, New York City, January 20, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1587)
  - Meeting with Business and Banking Leaders, Executive Mansion, January 21, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1588)
  - Luncheon at J. Burch McMorran's Home, January 21, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1589)
  - Dinner Preceding the Legislative Reception, Executive Mansion, January 21, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1590)
  - Legislative Reception, Executive Mansion, Albany, New York, January 21, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1591)
  - Concord, New Hampshire, January 24, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1592)
  - Breakfast Meeting, January 25, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1593)
  - Republican GO-Day Rally, Closed Circuit, Palladium, Los Angeles, California, January 29, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1594)
  - After Dinner Speech, Los Angeles, California, January 29, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1595)
  - Lincoln Day Dinner Medford Armory, Medford, Oregon, February 7, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1596)
  - Dinner, Legislative Correspondents and Wives, Executive Mansion, Albany, New York, February 18, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1597)
  - Associated Industries Luncheon, Executive Mansion, Albany, February 18, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1598)
  - Court of Appeals Dinner, Executive Mansion, Albany, February 18, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1599)
  - Dinner Party Legislative Correspondents' Wives, March 14, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1600)
  - Luncheon, State University Trustees, March 16, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1601)
  - Reception for French Consul General M. Michel Legendre, March 23, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1602)
  - Dinner for Republican Governors, 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington, D. C., April 9, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1603)
  - 12th Anual Republican Women's Conference, Washington, D. C., April 9, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1604)
  - Buffet Supper, 812 5th Avenue, New York City, April 23, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1605)
  - Counsel's Dinner, Executive Mansion, Albany, New York, April 24, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1606)
  - McArthur Court, University of Oregon, Eugene, Oregon, May 3, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1607)
  - Luncheon for New York State Republican Committee, Biltmore, New York City, May 6, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1608)
  - Luncheon, Channel City Club, Miramar Hotel, Santa Barbara, California, May 26, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1609)
  - Luncheon, Monterey County Fairgrounds, Monterey, California, May 28, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1610)
  - Commonwealth Club Luncheon, San Francisco, California, May 29, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1611)
  - Huntington Station Dinner Sponsored by Suffolk County Republican Committee, June 4, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1612)
  - Speaker Joseph Carlino Scholarship Fund Dinner, Lido Beach, New York, June 25, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1613)
  - Governor Rockefeller's Statement to the Committee on Resolution of the 1964 Republican National Convention, July 7, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1614)
  - Resolutions on Subject of Extremism, July 14, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1615)
  - Interview of Governor by Bill Beutel, ABC, Sheraton Palace Hotel, San Francisco, California, July 15, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1616)
  - Cabinet Luncheon, September 21, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1617)
  - Rally - Citizens Committee to Save Brooklyn Naval Shipyard - Madison Square Garden, October 4, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1618)
  - Luncheon Meeting of Finance and Advisory Committee on Traffic, November 16, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1619)
  - Chief State School Officers, November 18, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1620)
  - Reception for Chief State School Officers, Knickerbocker Club, New York City, November 18, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1621)
  - Governor's Remarks, National Council of Chief State School Officers, November 18, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1622)
  - Luncheon for Broadcasters Association, New York City, November 23, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1623)
  - Republican Governor's Conference, Denver, Colorado, December 3-5, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1624)
  - Rome-Utica Chamber of Commerce Luncheon, Utica, New York, December 10, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1625)
  - Mansion, 4:00 P.M., Reception for Electoral College, December 14, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1626)
  - Luncheon for Elected and Newly Elected Legislators, Schine Ten Eyck, December 16, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1627)
  - Cabinet Luncheon Meeting at Mansion (Canceled), December 22, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1628)
  - Executive Staff Christmas Reception, Mansion, December 22, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1629)
  - Official Opening of Office of General Service's Computer Center - Albany, December 22, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1630)
  - Not Used (Box 57, Folder 1631)
  - Buffet Following Opening of 1965 Legislature, Executive Mansion, January 6, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 1632)
  - United Nations Party, January 10, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 1633)
  - Transcript of Interview "Your Governor Reports", January 10, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 1634)
  - Annual Meeting of the New York State Agricultural Society, Albany, New York, January 13, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 1635)
  - Regional Development Dinner, Hotel Jamestown, Jamestown, New York, January 14, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 1636)
  - Regional Development Luncheon, Hotel Statler-Hilton, Buffalo, New York, January 14, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 1637)
  - Luncheon for Board of Directors of New York State Science and Technology Foundation, New York City, January 15, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1638)
  - Cabinet Luncheon, January 18, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1639)
  - 2nd Annual Legislative Luncheon Meeting of New York State Association for Mental Health, Albany, January 19, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1640)
  - Washington Itinerary, January 19-20, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1641)
  - Memorial Service for Dr. Paul H. Hoch, New York Academy of Medicine, New York City, January 21, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1642)
  - Labor Leaders Meeting and Luncheon, Executive Mansion, 12:00 Noon, Albany, New York, January 25, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1643)
  - Annual Budget Luncheon, Executive Mansion, 12:30 PM, Albany, New York, January 27, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1644)
  - Women's National Republican Club Luncheon, Waldorf Astoria, New York City (Governor Did Not Atend), January 30, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1645)
  - Budget Conference for Republican Members of the Legislature, Red Room, Capitol, Albany, February 1, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1646)
  - Parade Magazine "Scenic Highway Award" DeWitt Clinton, Albany, New York, February 2, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1647)
  - Address to New York State Republican County Chairmen and Vice Chairmen, Ten-Eyck Hotel, Albany, February 8, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1648)
  - Visit to the Veterans Hospitals and Domiciliary at Bath, New York, February 11, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1649)
  - Associeted Industries Luncheon, February 18, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1650)
  - Governor Rockefeller's Statement Regarding Water Pollution Control, Washington, D. C., February 23, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1651)
  - Legislative Dinner, Executive Mansion, 7:00 PM, February 23, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1652)
  - Legislative Reception, Executive Mansion, 9:00 PM, February 23, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1653)
  - Campaign Committee Meeting, Executive Mansion, March 2, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1654)
  - Associated Industries of New York State Luncheon at the Executive Mansion, 12:30 PM, March 3, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1655)
  - Statement by Governor Rockefeller re Discussion of Levitt's 1st Budget "Study", March 6, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1656)
  - Meeting in Small Conference Room, March 8, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1657)
  - Republican Coordinating Council, Washington, D. C., March 10, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1658)
  - Department of Labor Tape, March 15, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1659)
  - Dinner for the Court of Appeals, Executive Mansion, Albany, New York, March 16, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1660)
  - 181st Anniversary Dinner the Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick of New York City, Hotel - Astoria, New York City, March 17, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1661)
  - Legislative Correspondents Association (LCA) Dinner and Show, March 20, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1662)
  - Annual State Convention, New York State National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), Wilborn Temple, Albany, New York, March 23, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1663)
  - Luncheon with Labor Leaders, 812 5th Avenue, New York, New York, March 25, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1664)
  - Spring Conference of the County Officers Association Meeting (Canceled), March 30, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1665)
  - Remarks by Governor Rockefeller at Luncheon - Greater Watertown Chamber of Commerce, April 1, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1666)
  - Luncheon for the Administrative Council of the Department of Labor, Executive Mansion, April 7, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1667)
  - Dinner for TV Stations Personnel in Appreciation for "Executive Chamber Series", Executive Mansion, Albany, New York, April 12, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1668)
  - Sixth Annual National Assembly, The American National Theater and Academy, New York City, April 26, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1669)
  - Opening Night of the Kingston Lions Club Annual Exposition and Home Show, Kingston, New York, April 27, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1670)
  - Campaign Dinner of the Mount Sinai School of Medicine Grand Ballroom, Hotel Pierre, New York City, April 28, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1671)
  - Governors' Conference on Problems of Pollution in the Great, May 10, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1672)
  - 3rd Annual Institute, Capital District Chapter of the American Society for Public Administration, May 11, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1673)
  - South Mall Financing Agreement Signing Ceremony, Red Room, Albany, New York, May 11, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1674)
  - Pure Water Legislation Signing Ceremony, Red Room, State Capitol, May 12, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1675)
  - Dinner for the Board of Trustees of the State University of New York, 812 5th Avenue, New York City, May 12, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1676)
  - Opening Ceremonies of the Youth Opportunity Center, Albany, New York, May 18, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1677)
  - New York State Women's Civil Defense Council, May 18, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1678)
  - Foreign Consuls Reception, New York State Pavilion, World's Fair Grounds, New York, New York, May 20, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1679)
  - Dinner in Honor of Carl Spad, Executive Mansion, May 21, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1680)
  - Governor Rockefeller Accepts Presentation from Fashion Institute of Technology, New York City, May 24, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1681)
  - Dinner at 812 5th Avenue Apartment, New York City, May 26, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1682)
  - Meeting with Representative of General Electric, June 7, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1683)
  - Dinner with Amory Houghton, June 15, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1684)
  - NAR Visit to Rockland County, June 15, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1685)
  - Drop in at Tappan Zee Historical Society, Orangetown, New York, in Rockland County, June 15, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1686)
  - New York State Conference of Mayors, Hotel Manager, Rochester, New York, June 16, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1687)
  - National Conference of Arts Councils of America, American Symphony Orchestra League, Washington, D. C., June 18, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1688)
  - Cornerstone Ceremony for the South Mall Project, Albany, New York, June 21, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1689)
  - Governor's Library Conference, Shine Ten Eyck Hotel, Albany, New York, June 24, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1690)
  - Awards to Psychiatric Aides, State Capitol, Albany, New York, June 24, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1691)
  - Maid of the Mist Tenth Annual Festival and Ball, July 16, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1692)
  - Smithtown Tercentenary Celebration and Parade, August 8, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1693)
  - Cocktail Party for Sol Corbin, September 15, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1694)
  - Albany Chamber of Commerce Pure Waters Program, September 17, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1695)
  - Convocation at the State University at Genesco, September 17, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1696)
  - Tupper Lake Women's Republican Club, Tupper Lake, New York, September 22, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1697)
  - Dedication Belgian Line Terminal East River, Clinton Street, New York, New York, September 24, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1698)
  - Dedication John Jay Homestead, Katonah, New York, September 24, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1699)
  - 51st Annual Meeting Associated Industries of New York State, Whiteface Inn, New York, September 24, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1700)
  - Welcoming Address, Associated Press Managing Editors Convention, Buffalo, New York, September 29, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1701)
  - North-South Expressway Interstate Route 81, 1000 Island Bridge, Jefferson County, New York, September 29, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1702)
  - Dedication of New York Campus, Jefferson Community College, Watertown, New York, September 29, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1703)
  - 16th Annual Convention Banquet of the National Association for Retarded Children, New York, New York, September 29, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1704)
  - Dinner for Sponsorship Committee Membership Group, 812 5th Avenue, New York City, October 4, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1705)
  - 75th Anniversary Convocation, College of Idaho, Caldwell, Idaho, October 7, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1706)
  - Completion of Inner Loop, Rochester, New York, October 20, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1707)
  - Dinner Meeting Buffalo Academy of Medicine, Hotel Statler-Hilton, Buffalo, New York, October 20, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1708)
  - Susquehanna River Basin Committee Binghamton, October 20, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1709)
  - Dedication Nicholas J. Strozzi Building, Buffalo State Hospital, Buffalo, New York, October 21, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1710)
  - Dedication, Cell and Virus Building, Roswell Park Memorial Institute, Buffalo, New York, October 21, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 1711)
  - Luncheon, Women's Committee, Buffalo, New York, October 21, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 1712)
  - Mansion Buffet, October 21, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 1713)
  - Governors' Club, October 21, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 1714)
  - 5th Anniversary Office of General Services, Albany, New York, October 21, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 1715)
  - Governors' Club, Cocktails-Buffet, 6-7 o'clock PM, Executive Mansion, Albany, New York, October 21, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 1716)
  - Informal Election Night Party, 812 5th Avenue, New York City, November 2, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 1717)
  - Luncheon for Westchester County Legislators, Pocantico Hills, New York, November 13, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 1718)
  - Pure Waters Meeting, State Capital, Red Room, 2 PM, Albany, New York, November 16, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 1719)
  - Regional Planning Luncheon, Hotel Van Curler - Albany, New York, November 17, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 1720)
  - Letters to Those Agreeing to Serve as Advisors to the Chairman of the Finance Committee, November 23, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 1721)
  - Meeting with Ad Hoc Committee to Discuss Problems of Negro Community, Music Hall, New York City, November 26, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 1722)
  - Republican Governors' Meeting, 7:30 PM, Washington, D. C., December 12, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 1723)
  - 11:00 AM Meeting with Representatives from New York City, Nassau, Suffolk, Rockland and Westchester School Boards Association, December 22, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 1724)
  - Mayor Lindsay Inaugural, New York City, January 1, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 1725)
  - Buffet Luncheon After Opening of the Legislature, Executive Mansion, January 5, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 1726)
  - Meeting and Supper, Six New England Governors and Wives (Cancelled), January 6, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 1727)
  - National Award of National Wildlife Federation, Washington, D. C., January 11, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 1728)
  - Banking Advisory Committee Luncheon, Mansion, January 11, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 1729)
  - List of Persons Invited to: Discussion of Budget for Fiscal 1966-67 (Flat List and Draft), January 16, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 1730)
  - Budget School Executive Mansion, January 16, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 1731)
  - Breakfast Meeting with Nassau Members of Legislature, Executive Mansion, Albany, January 18, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 1732)
  - Meeting to Set Up Map Plans for Constitutional Convention - St. Regis Hotel, New York City, January 20, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 1733)
  - Meeting with New Assemblyman from Oneida County Edward Hanna, January 21, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 1734)